Damn what wet and moisture and ...
It was Valkyria, now we are going to Loke.
I never went it.
Of all the attractions at Liseberg, Loke is my favorite.
Spin back and forth, wonderful.
"Put your hands up in the air, put your hands up!"
- Why am I so dad?
Up with your hand!
Oh damn!
My God what fun!
This is a big favorite.
My God what good it is.
You should not drink lots of beer and go this one.
Eh, two stuff?
Very value for money!
- We have traveled Loke, Colorado and Balder.
Which one won Erika?
- Loke was a hit.
Loke was nice, I went with it.
What is the plan with the evening, are you singles?
The plan is to be curved and have it good!
- Yes!
And then?
- We shall see!
[Inaudible]
If you were to rat-a visitors ... Do you like girls or guys?
Girls!
- I keep it unnamed.
Unsaminated?
Yes but that's good.